questproteinbar.com 2015-12-09

# Privacy Policy

* Quest Nutrition, LLC ("Quest") is committed to providing you with quality goods and excellent customer service. This privacy policy explains how we collect, use, share, store and protect information that you provide to us. You agree to the terms of our privacy policy by using Quest’s website. You also agree to the terms of our privacy policy by using any page or feature in any other website that Quest has linked to this privacy policy.

Sometimes, Quest teams up with other companies to better serve you. Quest’s website may have a link to another company’s website or another company’s website may have a link to Quest’s website. Those other companies may have privacy policies that are different from Quest’s privacy policy. You should read those other companies’ privacy policies to understand their terms. To the extent any linked websites you visit are not a website owned by Quest, we are not responsible for their content, any use of the sites, or the privacy practices of those sites. 

* We collect personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide to us and by automated means. Personally identifiable information we collect and save that you provide voluntarily to us is your name, mailing and billing address, your telephone number and/or your e-mail address. We collect this personally identifiable information only when you actually voluntarily enter it on a page on our website or on a page on another website that is expressly linked to our website.

* We collect certain information by automated means when you visit our website, such as how many users visited our sites and the pages accessed. By collecting this information, we learn how to best tailor our website to our visitors. We collect this information through various means such as cookies, web beacons and IP addresses, as explained below. We also collect some personally identifiable information by automated means, such as collecting your IP address when you access our website.

* Like many companies, we use cookies on our website. Cookies are bits of text that are placed on your computer’s hard drive when you visit certain websites. We use cookies to tell us, for example, whether you have visited us before or if you are a new visitor and to help us identify site features in which you may have the greatest interest. Cookies may enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular site. Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all our website features.

* Certain pages on our website contain web beacons (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). These web beacons allow third parties to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the information in cookies set by the third party. We use this information to analyze trends, to track users’ movements around the sites and to gather demographic information as a whole. We do not provide personal information through these cookies or web beacon to any third party nor do any third parties collect any personal information by these means. Our website does not respond to do not track (DNT) signals.

* An IP address is personally identifiable information that is a unique identifier that certain electronic devices use to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet. When you visit our website, we may view and collect the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet. We use this information to determine the general physical location of the device. We also may use this information to enhance our website.

* Your personally identifiable information will only be used in the following ways unless otherwise stated at the time you provide it to us: 

A. We will use it to contact you in order to answer questions, send you requested information, send you free or discount offers, and keep you updated on our company and its products.

B. We will use it to process orders you may place for our products.

C. We may use it for Quest’s internal purposes. These purposes include administration of our website, data analytics and compliance with our legal obligations, policies and procedures.

D. We use it to provide an enhanced and more personalized online experience.

* Our site may contain announcements of promotions or contests that we are conducting which you may sometimes enter electronically. We use information you provide us when you enter to conduct the promotion or contests (for example, to notify winners). We won’t use the information you provide for any other purpose unless you agree to let us do so.

* Your personally identifiable information that you disclose to us is stored in our secure server’s database. The information is only accessed by those persons authorized to access our systems, and they are required to keep the information confidential.

If you open an online order account with us, it will contain personally identifiable information that you have entered into your account. You can access your account online via our website’s log in function and update or delete all of your information except for your default address which can be edited but not deleted. You can also choose not to store your address information in your account, but it will be contained in your order history. 

We offer an auto delivery subscription service that automatically delivers Quest products to you on a schedule you select. You will enter personally identifiable information into your subscription to use this service. You can edit/delete/update your auto delivery subscriptions. You can also use a function called TURN ON/TURN OFF which saves the subscription and allows you to turn it on at your preference. Our payment processor will save a unique token identifier, but not your credit card information.

You can opt in to receive our newsletters and we will use your email address to deliver our newsletters to you. You can unsubscribe from our newsletters whenever you want.

* We do not sell or otherwise disclose information about our website visitors, except as described here. We may share the information you provide among our subsidiaries and affiliates and with our joint marketing partners. We may also share the information with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf. These service providers are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements. In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity. If you are a California resident, you may ask us to refrain from sharing your information with third parties for their marketing purposes. Please tell us your preference by contacting us as indicated in the “How to Contact Us” section of this Privacy Notice. We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use information you have provided through our website in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice.

* Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. 

* We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

* The effective date of this privacy policy is 08/21/2015. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page by updating this policy.

* We value our relationship with you. If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, or want to communicate with us for any reason regarding it, please contact us via e-mail at: Business&LegalAffairs@questnutrition.com
